JOSEPH E. PERSICO PAPERS (APAP030) 1910-2003
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
1969 October 29 Cornwall, NY, Excerpts, Mid-Hudson Regional Development Luncheon
1969 October 29 Newburgh, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking at Newburgh Lake St. Houses
1969 November 5 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Dinner Honoring Duke of Edinburgh
1969 November 6 Excerpts, Opening Ceremony of New Mary Manning Walsh Home
1969 November 6 Queens, NY, Press Release, Queens Chamber of Commerce
1969 November 9 Flushing, NY, Excerpts, Celebration in Honor of Rabbi Mowshowitz
1969 November 9 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Dinner for Restoration of the Yeshiva and Mesivta
1969 November 14 New York City, NY, Press Release, Gold Medal Award of the West Side Chamber of Commerce
1969 November 19 Binghamton, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Binghamton Civic Center
1969 November 19 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 40th Anniversary Dinner of Regional Planning Association
1969 November 19 Binghamton, NY, Press Release, Route 17 Association
1969 November 20 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, Antennial Banquet of Canisius College
1969 November 24 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Narcotic Addiction Control Commission Conference
1969 November 24 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking Ceremony of 63rd Street Tunnel
1969 November 25 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Memorandum of Intent New Haven Commuter Service
1969 November 25 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Annual Dinner of St. Vincent's Hall
1969 December 2 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, National Press Club Luncheon
1969 December 4 Jackson Heights, NY, Excerpts, Lexington School of the Deaf
1969 December 5 New York City, NY, Annual Governors Luncheon
1969 December 8 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of First Phase Harlem River
1969 December 9 Albany, NY, Statement, Regarding US Senate Seat, Followed by a Press Conference
1969 December 10 Buffalo, NY, Press Release, Erie County Republican Committee Dinner
1969 December 25 Rochester, NY, Film Interview, With Glover Delaney WHEC-TV
1970
1970 January 5 White Plains, NY, Excerpts of Remarks, Inauguration of Edwin G. Michaelian
1970 January 13 Albany, NY, Excerpts of Remarks, Methodone Maintenance Program
1970 January 14 Albany, NY, Excerpts of Remarks, Educational Finance
1970 January 14 Albany, NY, Press Release, Century Farm Citations
1970 January 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Dinner Honoring Louis Lefkowitz
1970 January 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Memorial Service for Martin Luther King, Jr.
1970 January 17 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Testimonial Dinner for the New York District and New York State Council for Carpenters
1970 January 20 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Budget School Briefing
1970 January 22 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Printing Industries of American Dinner
1970 January 28 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking of Bronx Community College
1970 January 29 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York State Water Pollution Control Association Dinner
1970 January 29 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Westchester County Republican Committee Dinner
1970 January 30 Albany, NY, Press Release, Letter to Cahill and Dempsey
1970 January 30 New York City, NY, Remarks, Women's National Republican Party
1970 February 2 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Swearing in of Joseph Swidler
1970 February 2 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Long Island Rail Road
1970 February 4 New York City, NY, Address, Harvard Business School Club
1970 February 4 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Harvard Business School Club
1970 February 4 New York City, NY, Dews Conference, Improve Service on Penn Central
1970 February 10 New York City, NY, Excerpts, SUNY Board of Regents
1970 February 11 Staten Island, NY, Remarks, Richmond County Republican Committee
1970 February 13 Batavia, NY, Remarks, New York State School for the Blind
1970 February 13 Rochester, NY, Interview, Monroe County Airport
1970 February 13 Rochester, NY, TV Taping, WHEC-TV
1970 February 18 New York City, NY, Announcement, Agreement and Westchester County
1970 February 20 Syracuse, NY, TV News Conference, Hancock Airfield
1970 February 20 Syracuse, NY, TV Interview, WHEN-TV
1970 February 23 Albany, NY, Q and A Session, Business and Professional Club
1970 February 23 Albany, NY, Statement, Bill Signing Mass Transit
1970 February 23 Albany, NY, Address, New York State Council of Churches
1970 February 24 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Builders Association
1970 February 24 Albany, NY, Excerpts, New York State Builders Association
1970 February 24 Poughkeepsie, NY, Remarks, Chamber of Commerce
1970 February 24 Albany, NY, Excerpts, 23rd Annual Legislative Dinner
1970 February 25 Washington, D.C., News Interview, Washington Library
1970 February 25 Washington, D.C., Questions by War, Governors Conference
1970 February 25 Washington, D.C., News Conference, Committee Chairman's Conference
1970 February 26 Washington, D.C., TV Interview, Discussion of Government Conference
1970 March 3 Albany, NY, Press Conference, Q and A Session in Red Room at Capitol
1970 March 3 Albany, NY, News Interview, Discussion and County Leaders
1970 March 3 Albany, NY, Excerpts, League of Women Voters
1970 March 4 Kingston, NY, Remarks, Delaware Republican Committee
1970 March 4 Poughkeepsie, NY, Meeting of Rockefeller with Student Leaders
1970 March 4 Margaretville, NY, Remarks, Delaware Republican Committee
1970 March 5 Binghamton, NY, Remarks, Broome County Republican Committee
1970 March 5 Binghamton, NY, TV Interview, WNBF-TV
1970 March 6 Albany, NY, Remarks, Nassau County Executive Committee
1970 March 6 New York City, NY, Remarks, Metropolitan Republican Club
1970 March 8 New York City, NY, Remarks, AME Zion Church
1970 March 8 New York City, NY, Excerpts, United Aids Service
1970 March 9 Saratoga, NY, Remarks, Saratoga Republican Committee
1970 March 10 Albany, NY, Remarks, New York State Broadcasters Inc.
1970 March 10 Albany, NY, Monty Hall Following Rockefeller
1970 March 12 Albany, NY, Address, Schenectady Republican Committee
1970 March 12 Johnstown, NY, Remarks, Fulton Republican Committee
1970 March 12 Albany, NY, TV Interview, WTEN-TV "Face to Face"
1970 March 13 Plattsburgh, NY, Address, Dedication of Plattsburgh State College
1970 March 13 Plattsburgh, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Plattsburgh State College
1970 March 13 Plattsburgh, NY, Interview, After SUNY Dedication
1970 March 13 Plattsburgh, NY, TV Interview, Regarding Art
1970 March 13 Burlington, VT, TV Interview, WCAX-TV
1970 March 13 Syracuse, NY, Excerpt of TV Interview at Airport
1970 March 13 Syracuse, NY, Excerpt, New York Press Association
1970 March 18 New York City, NY, International Supreme Council
1970 March 19 New York City, NY, Address, United Jewish Appeal
1970 March 19 New York City, NY, Excerpts, United Jewish Appeal
1970 March 23 Albany, NY, Remarks, Teenage Republicans
1970 March 23 Albany, NY, Press Interview, Q and A Session
1970 March 23 Albany, NY, Excerpts, SUNY Albany Seminar
1970 March 23 Albany, NY, Swearing in of Bob Connor
1970 March 25 Albany, NY, Press Release, Letter to George P. Schulz
1970 April 1 New York City, NY, Excerpts, New York Rabbis Installation Ceremony
1970 April 2 New York City, NY, Bill Signing New York City School District
1970 April 8 Sodus, NY, Address, Wayne County Civic Leaders
1970 April 8 Rochester, NY, Remarks, Kick-Off 1970 Campaign
1970 April 8 Canandaigua, NY, Address, Ontario County Republican Committee
1970 April 8 Canandaigua, NY, Press Conference, Q and A Session
1970 April 9 Albany, NY, Press Release, Letter to Samuel Gould
1970 April 10 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Mid-City Republican Club
1970 April 10 New York City, NY, Man of the Year Award
1970 April 10 New York City, NY, Interview, With Barry Gray
1970 April 10 New York City, NY, Proclamation, Histadrut Golden Annual Week
1970 April 10 New York City, NY, News Conference, Histadrut Golden Annual Week
1970 April 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, Rockefeller and Ambassador Arbin
1970 April 14 New York City, Excerpts, Testimonial Dinner for Gus Levy
1970 April 15 Albany, NY, Interview, Rockefeller and Senator Brydes
1970 April 16 Great Neck, NY, Remarks, Temple Israel Annual Dinner
1970 April 21 Syracuse, NY, Dedication of Onondaga Community College
1970 April 21 New York City, NY, TV Interview, with Bob Lape WABC
1970 April 21 New York City, NY, TV Interview, with Gabe Pressman WWBC
1970 April 21 New York City, NY, TV Interview, with Jerry Wilson WCBS
1970 April 21 New York City, NY, Taped Interview, with Victor Rissel
1970 April 22 Albany, NY, Bill Signing Department of Environmental Conservation
1970 April 22 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Earth Day Teach-In
1970 April 22 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Earth Day Rally
1970 April 23 New York City, NY, Interview, with Martha Dean of WOR Radio
1970 April 23 New York City, NY, Excerpt of Press Interview, WOR Studio
1970 April 23 New York City, NY, NAR Endorsement by Trades Council
1970 April 24 New City, NY, Remarks, Rockland County Republican Committee
1970 April 24 New City, NY, Excerpts, Hold Key Club Breakfast
1970 April 24 New City, NY, News Interview, Ripples of Rockland
1970 April 27 Alfred, NY, Remarks, SUNY Alfred
1970 April 27 Wellsville, NY, Remarks, Joint Service Club
1970 April 27 Buffalo, NY, Bill Signing Donovan Office Building
1970 April 27 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, Republican Committee Fund Raiser
1970 April 27 Wellsville, NY, Excerpts, Joint Service Club Luncheon
1970 April 27 Alfred, NY, Excerpts, 5th Annual Convocation at SUNY Alfred
1970 April 28 New York City, NY, Swearing in of Milton Lugar
1970 April 29 New York City, NY, Bill Signing Teachers Retirement Pension
1970 April 29 New York City, NY, Address, New York Academy of Medicine
1970 April 30 Astoria, NY, Remarks, Queens County Republican Committee
1970 April 30 Astoria, NY, Excerpts, Queens County Republican Committee
1970 April 30 New York City, NY, TV Interview, Institute of International Education
1970 April 30 New York City, NY, Remarks, Institute of International Education
1970 April 30 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Institute of International Education
1970 May 1 New York City, NY, Conference on Aging
1970 May 1 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Conference on Aging
1970 May 5 New York City, NY, Address, Greater New York Hospital Association
1970 May 5 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Interfaith Convocation on Drug Abuse
1970 May 5 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Greater New York Hospital Association
1970 May 6 New York City, NY, Bill Signing Division of Penn Central
1970 May 7 Eastchester, NY, Remarks, Westchester County Republican Club
1970 May 7 Eastchester, NY, Excerpts, Westchester County Republican Club
1970 May 7 New York City, NY, Address, Whitney Young Director of the Urban League
1970 May 7 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 5th Annual Frederick Douglass Award
1970 May 10 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Anti Defamation League
1970 May 12 Bronx, NY, Remarks, Real Estate Board
1970 May 12 Bronx, NY, Remarks, Groundbreaking Promenade Apartments
1970 May 12 Bronx, NY, Excerpts, Groundbreaking Promenade Apartments
1970 May 12 New York City, NY, Bill Signing Drug Abuse
1970 May 12 New York City, NY, Bill Signing Mortgage Money
1970 May 12 New York City, NY, Swearing in Thornton Edward
1970 May 12 New York City, NY, Bill Signing Pension for AJ Kraus
1970 May 12 New York City, NY, Bill Signing Freedom of Information for Newsmen
1970 May 12 Bronx, NY, Excerpt, Sunrise Semester Breakfast
1970 May 12 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Catholic Interracial Council
1970 May 13 New York City, NY, Swearing in members of New York State Parole Board
1970 May 13 Washington, D.C., Press Interview, Rockefeller and New York State Congressional and State Delegates
1970 May 14 Bronx, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Kittay House
1970 May 14 Lewiston, NY, Remarks, Niagara Performing Arts Center
1970 May 14 Lewiston, NY, Excerpts, Niagara Performing Arts Center
1970 May 14 Lewiston, NY, Bill Signing New York State Burn Care Institute
1970 May 14 Niagara Falls, NY, Intro, Senator Brydges at County Republican Committee
1970 May 14 Buffalo, NY, Television Interview, following Cultural Arts Awards
1970 May 14 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, New York State Council on the Arts
1970 May 14 Niagara Falls, NY, Excerpts, Niagara County Republican Committee
1970 May 14 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Kittay House Dedication
1970 May 15 New York City, NY, Governors Conference on Health and Hospitals
1970 May 15 New York City, NY, News Conference, Rockefeller and Joseph Wilson
1970 May 15 Geneseo, NY, Remarks, Livingston County Republican Committee
1970 May 15 Geneseo, NY, Excerpts, Livingston, County Republican Committee
1970 May 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Arden House Conference
1970 May 16 Ithaca, NY, Address, Commencement Ceremony Ithaca College
1970 May 16 Ithaca, NY, Excerpts, Commencement Ceremony Ithaca College
1970 May 16 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Association for Help of Retarded Children
1970 May 18 New York City, NY, Remarks, Governors Conference on Scholastic Achievement
1970 May 19 New York City, NY, Remarks, American Insurance Association
1970 May 19 New York City, NY, Excerpts, American Insurance Association
1970 May 19 New York City, NY, News Conference, Rockefeller and Fioravante Perrotta
1970 May 19 New York City, NY, Television Interview, Following News Conference
1970 May 19 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Rockefelelr and Fioravante Perrotta
1970 May 20 Potsdam, NY, Remarks, Chamber of Commerce Dinner
1970 May 20 Potsdam, NY, Excerpts, Chamber of Commerce Dinner
1970 May 20 Potsdam, NY, Q and A Session at SUNY Potsdam
1970 May 20 New York City, NY, Excerpts, 25th Anniversary UN Convocation
1970 May 21 New York City, NY, Press Conference, AFL Endorsement of Musicians
1970 May 21 Watertown, NY, Excerpts, Cornerstone Ceremony
1970 May 23 Beacon, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Hudson Highland St. Park
1970 May 23 Beacon, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Hudson Highland St. Park
1970 May 25 New York City, Remarks, Conference on Environmental Pollution
1970 May 25 New York City, Excerpts, Conference on Environmental Pollution
1970 May 25 New York City, News Interview, Following Conference on Environmental Pollution
1970 May 25 New York City, Excerpts, New York County Republican Committee Reception
1970 May 26 Albany, NY, Remarks, Community Mental Health Board
1970 May 26 Albany, NY, Remarks, Dedication of New York State Police Academy
1970 May 26 Guilderland, NY, TELEVISION Interview, Dedication of Power Pool Center
1970 May 26 Guilderland, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Power Pool Center
1970 May 26 Guilderland, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Power Pool Center
1970 May 26 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Community Mental Health Board
1970 May 26 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of New York State Police Academy
1970 May 26 Amsterdam, NY, Excerpts, Montgomery County Republican Committee Dinner
1970 May 27 New York City, NY, Remarks, Committee to Employ the Handicapped
1970 May 27 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Committee to Employ the Handicapped
1970 May 28 Long Island, NY, Excerpts, Nassau County Republican Committee Dinner
1970 May 28 Queens, NY, Excerpts, Dedication Cross Bay Partway Bridge
1970 May 29 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Organization of Caribbean Americans
1970 June 1 New York City, NY, News Interview, Reception for Labor
1970 June 2 New York City, NY, TELEVISION Interview, Dedication of Robert Moses Plaza
1970 June 2 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Robert Moses Plaza
1970 June 3 New York City, NY, Rockefeller and Anti-War and Racist and Liberation Committee
1970 June 3 New York City, NY, Remarks, Luncheon Honoring Apollo 13 Astronauts
1970 June 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Luncheon Honoring Apollo 13 Astronauts
1970 June 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, American Association of Museums
1970 June 3 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Conference of Mayors
1970 June 4 New York City, NY, Remarks, Republican State Committee Luncheon
1970 June 4 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Republican State Committee Luncheon
1970 June 6 Tarrytown, NY, Remarks, Tarrytown Centennial
1970 June 6 Tarrytown, NY, Excerpts, Tarrytown Centennial
1970 June 8 Buffalo, NY, Remarks, 65th Health Conference
1970 June 8 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, 65th Health Conference
1970 June 8 Buffalo, NY, Remarks, Urban Development Corporation
1970 June 8 Buffalo, NY, Reverend Hemphill's Response after Urban Development Corporation
1970 June 8 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, Construction Start Ceremony Waterfront
1970 June 8 Buffalo, NY, Remarks, Licensed Practical Nurses of New York
1970 June 9 New York City, NY, Television Interview, Division of Housing and Community Renewal
1970 June 9 New York City, NY, Remarks, Division of Housing and Community Renewal
1970 June 9 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Division of Housing and Community Renewal
1970 June 10 Washington, D.C., Address, Republican Candidates on Campaign
1970 June 10 Washington, D.C., Excerpts, Conference Congressional Candidates
1970 June 10 Long Island, NY, Excerpt, Suffolk County Republican Committee Reception
1970 June 11 New York City, NY, News Conference, International Longshoremen
1970 June 12 Farmingdale, LI, Address, Commencement at SUNY Farmingdale
1970 June 12 Woodbury, LI, Remarks, Robert Moses Honoring WAR
1970 June 12 Westbury, LI, Remarks, Long Island Labor Leaders Honoring WAR
1970 June 14 Liberty, NY, Excerpts, National Federation of Jewish Men's Clubs
1970 June 15 Suffern, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Gligy Pharmaceutical
1970 June 15 Suffern, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Gligy Pharmaceutical
1970 June 15 New York City, NY, Address, Conference on Industry and Environment
1970 June 16 New York City, Excerpts, Conference on Industry and Environment
1970 June 16 New York City, News Conference, Conference on Industry and Environment
1970 June 18 New York City, NY, Uniformed Firemen's Association Endorsement of Rockefeller
1970 June 18 New York City, NY, Swearing in of the Honorable R.E. Fischen
1970 June 18 Long Island, NY, Remarks, Queen Child Guidance Center
1970 June 18 Long Island, NY, Excerpts, Queen Child Guidance Center
1970 June 18 New York City, NY, Excerpts, American Institute of Rapid Transit
1970 June 19 New York City, NY, Endorsement of Rockefeller by National Leather AFL
1970 June 19 Liberty, NY, Remarks, Order of AHEPH Annual Convention
1970 June 19 Liberty, NY, Excerpts, Order of AHEPH Annual Convention
1970 June 21 Brooklyn, NY, Remarks, Dedication of United Culavitchen Yeshivoth
1970 June 21 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of United Culavitchen Yeshivoth
1970 June 21 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Painters Union Dinner for S. Frank Raftery
1970 June 22 Buffalo, NY, Remarks, New York State Institute on Alcohol Problems
1970 June 22 Buffalo, NY, Excerpts, Summer Seminar at SUNY at Buffalo on Alcohol Problems
1970 June 22 Buffalo, NY, TV Interview, SUNY at Buffalo
1970 June 22 Buffalo, NY, Creative Education Medal awarded Dr. Guilford
1970 June 22 Albany, NY, Signing agreement of Urban Development Corporation and Albany
1970 June 23 New York City, NY, TV Interview, With Gabe Pressman
1970 June 23 New York City, NY, Toymakers International Union Endorsement of Rockefeller
1970 June 24 New York City, NY, TV Interview, New York State Democratic Party Primary
1970 June 24 Annapolis, MD, TV Interview, Governors Conference
1970 June 24 Annapolis, MD, Statement, Peace in the Middle East
1970 June 24 Annapolis, MD, Interview, Governors Mid-Atlantic Conference
1970 June 24 Annapolis, MD, News Conference, Governors Mid-Atlantic Conference
1970 June 24 Annapolis, MD, Interview, With Doug Edelson Wins
1970 June 25 New York City, NY, Radio Interview, Swearing-in of Henry Diamond
1970 June 25 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Swearing-in of Henry Diamond
1970 June 25 New York City, NY, Remarks, Policemen's Benevolent Association
1970 June 25 New York City, NY, Remarks, United Jewish Appeal
1970 June 26 Bronx, NY, Remarks, Description of Co-op City
1970 June 26 Brooklyn, NY, Remarks, On Tour of Project Sites
1970 June 26 Brooklyn, NY, Excerpts, On Tour of Project Sites
1970 June 26 New York City, NY, Interview, Housing Financing
1970 June 26 Staten Island, NY, Remarks, Borough President Reception
1970 June 26 New York City, NY, Remarks, Battery Park City
1970 June 26 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Battery Park City
1970 June 27 New York City, NY, Interview, Outside Studio 3A NBC
1970 June 27 Long Island, NY, Excerpts, Dinner Honoring Perry Duryea
1970 June 29 Greenwich, NY, Remarks, Washington County Republican Committee
1970 June 29 Greenwich, NY, Excerpts, Washington County Republican Committee
1970 June 29 Saratoga, NY, Remarks, New York State Newspaper Editors
1970 June 29 Saratoga, NY, Excerpts, New York State Newspaper Editors
1970 June 29 Saratoga, NY, Press Interview, New York State Newspaper Editors
1970 June 29 Glens Falls, NY, Remarks, Warren County Republican Committee
1970 June 30 Glens Falls, NY, Endorsement of Rockefeller by New York State Bricklayers IUA
1970 June 30 Glens Falls, NY, Excerpts, Endorsement of Rockefeller by New York State Bricklayers IUA
1970 June 30 Lake George, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Lake George Institute
1970 June 30 Lake George, NY, Excerpts, Dedication of Lake George Institute
1970 June 30 Los Angeles, CA, TV Excerpt, Conversation and Richard M. Nixon
1970 July 1 New York City, NY, News Conference, Transfer of Surplus Funds to Transit Authority
1970 July 1 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Transfer of Surplus Funds to Transit Authority
1970 July 19 Albany, NY, Press Interview, Power Shortage
1970 July 20 New York City, NY, News Conference, Appointment of Mayor R. Wagner
1970 July 20 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Appointment of Mayor R. Wagner
1970 July 20 New York City, NY, TV Interview, Appointment of Mayor R. Wagner
1970 July 20 New York City, NY, Radio Interview, Appointment of Mayor R. Wagner
1970 July 20 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Arts and Entertainment
1970 July 20 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Arts and Entertainment
1970 July 20 Syracuse, NY, Address, Lecture Series at Maxwell Grade School
1970 July 20 Syracuse, NY, Excerpts, Lecture Series at Maxwell Grade School
1970 July 22 New York City, NY, Greetings to National Urban League
1970 July 22 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Greetings to National Urban League
1970 July 24 New York City, NY, Swearing in of S.J. Prezioso
1970 July 24 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Swearing in of S.J. Prezioso
1970 July 27 New York City, NY, Interview, with Jim Gash WNEW
1970 July 27 New York City, NY, New York City Republican Campaign
1970 July 27 New York City, NY, Remarks, Banco Popular de Puerto Rico
1970 July 27 New York City, NY, Excerpts, Banco Popular de Puerto Rico
1970 July 28 New York City, NY, Press Interview, Penn Central Community Service
1970 July 28 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Penn Central Fire
1970 July 28 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Rockefeller and Honorable S.J. Rosenman
1970 July 28 New York City, NY, News Interview, Endorsement of Rockefeller by Hon. Rosenman
1970 July 29 Rotterdam, Press Interview, Power Shortage, etc.
1970 July 29 Albany, NY, Statement, of Joe Swidler Public Service Commission
1970 July 29 Albany, NY, Television Interview, Allied Printing Trades Convention
1970 July 29 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Allied Printing Trades Convention
1970 July 29 Albany, NY, Excerpts, Chief of Police Annual Banquet
1970 July 30 Albany, NY, New Interview, Power and Pollution in New York City
1970 July 30 Latham, NY, Remarks, Meeting on Drug Abuse, Shaker High School
1970 July 30 Latham, NY, Excerpts, Meeting on Drug Abuse, Shaker High School
1970 July 30 Goshen, NY, Excerpts, Orange County Infirmary
1970 July 31 Valhalla, NY, Remarks, Meeting on Drug Abuse, Westchester Community College
1970 July 31 Valhalla, NY, Excerpts, Meeting on Drug Abuse, Westchester Community College
1970 August 3 New York City, NY, Press Interview, at Edgecombe Center